噢 德瑞克      抱歉 安珀
Oh,Drake.        I'm sorry,Amber.
布莱就是这样子 嘴巴不认输
It's just like Brad to have to have the last word.
对不起 我迟到了 怎么样了?      我们在看结局
I'm sorryI'm late.What happened?        We wanna see the end.
我要你 德瑞克      我知道
I want you, Drake.        I know you do.
但我们永远不会有结果的
But you and I can never be together that way.
什么?      有件事我一直没告诉过你
What?        There's something I never told you.
我其实是你的同父异母兄弟
I'm actually your half-brother.
什么?
What?
接下来怎么样了呢?
So,what happens next?
我帮连体婴做分割手术 得了医学奖
Well, I get the medical award for separating the Siamese twins.
然后安珀和我一起去委内瑞拉
Then Amber and I go to Venezuela
去见我们另一个同父异母兄弟 雷蒙...
to meet our other halfbrother,Ramon...
我在那里见到了世界最大的翡翠 那真的很大
and that's where I find the world's biggest emerald.It's really big.
但却受到了诅咒
But it's cursed.
好酷      天啊 好棒的节目
So cool!        God, that is good TV
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第15集
雷莫瑞医生之死 The One Where Dr Ramoray Dies
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：酱油
菲比 跟我玩啦      不要
Pheebs, play with me!        No!
这游戏太荒诞了
This game is grotesque.
把二十个手无寸铁的人 串成一长条...
Twenty armless guys joined at the waist by a steel bar...
被迫无止境地踢足球?
..forced to play soccer forever?
拜托 简直是侵害人权嘛
Hello? Human rights violation.
不用替他们难过 他们踢完球后...
Dont feel so bad. After they're done playing...
我会把小塑胶妞拿出来 大家都会很开心的啊
I break out the plastic women and everybody has a pretty good time.
你为什么不跟你的室友玩?
Why don't you play with your roommate?
他不太喜欢桌上足球
He's not a big fan of foosball.
你跟那个新来的处得不好吗
Are we not getting along with the new boy?
也不是 他只是很多时间都在自己的房间里
No,he's all right.He spends most of his time in his room.
或许是因为你还没花时间去了解他
Maybe because you haven't taken time to get to know him.
我们来补救一下
Let's remedy that, shall we?
我们不用补救      有必要 会很好玩的
We don't need to remedy that.        Oh, yeah, it'll be fun!
怎么了?      你好
What was that?        Hi!
我只是在想我们三个人一起喝点啤酒...
I thought it'd be fun if the three of us had beers...
彼此认识一下 应该会很不错
and got to know each other
好 听起来不错      太好了...
All right.That sounds all right.        Oh, good! Okay.
糟糕 我得走了 因为我还要赶去...
Oh,no,I have to go,because I'm late for my...
参加"绿蛋与火腿"的研讨会
Green Eggs and Ham discussion group.
今晚的题目是"为什么不在火车上吃呢?"
Tonight,it's "Why he would not eat them on a train?"
好好玩吧 再见      好烂的借口
Have fun! Bye!         That was so lame.
我知道啊
I know.
好好跟他聊啊
Okay talk to him.
你觉得那个赛车手被开了很多罚单还是...?
So you think that Speed Racer guy gets a lot of tickets or...?
真好笑 那么是谁甩了谁?
Thats good. So who broke up with who?
开什么玩笑?当然是我甩了她
You kidding? I broke up with her.
她真的以为西恩潘是柬埔寨的首都
She actually thought Sean Penn was the capital of Cambodia.
太好笑了 大家都知道 柬埔寨的首都是…
When everybody knows that the capital of Cambodia is...
不是西恩 潘就对了
It's not Sean Penn.
我有一个好笑的
All right, I got a funny one. All right?
我上一个女友 堤莉 我们正在吃早餐
My last girlfriend,Tilly.We'reeating breakfast,right?
我做了很多薄煎饼 大约有五十个
I made these pancakes.Like,50 pancakes.
突然间 她转过来对我说 艾迪...
All of a sudden she turns to me and says,"Eddie...
我不想再见到你了
I don't wanna see you anymore."
那就像是 她把手放进我的胸膛里...
It was literally like she had reached into my chest...
把心挖出来 把我的生活搞得一团乱
ripped out my heart and smeared it all over my life!
我像是掉进无止境的深渊
There was this incredible abyss and I'm falling.
我不断地往下掉 好像永远不会着地
I keep falling and I don't think I'm ever gonna stop!
这故事不太好笑 是不是?
That wasn't such a funny story,was it?
坏脾气的老头 说我会尽量
And a crusty old man Said I'll do what I can
其他老鼠开始摇沙铃
And the rest of the rats Played maracas
结束了 晚安
That's it!Thanks!Good night.
菲比还有别的工作 对吧?
Phoebe's got another job,right?
今晚很棒 菲比
Great set tonight,Pheebs.
我知道
I know
我们得走了
We should get going.
我们也是 我早上八点有病人
We should too.I've got patients at 8 in the morning.
我们每次都去你那边过夜
You know how we always stay at your apartment?
今晚或许可以改在我这边啊
I thought tonight we'd stay at my place.
我不知道 我没带睡衣
I dont know.I don't have my jammies.
或许你不需要
You don't need them.
各位 这是我的小妹
My baby sister,ladies and gentlemen.
闭嘴 我开心就好
Shut up.I'm happy.
太棒了 我必须得说几句
Oh this is so nice!I have to make a speech.
我只想说...
I just want to say...
在摩妮卡交往过的为数众多的男友当中...
Of all the guys that Monica has been with,and that is a lot...
我最喜欢你
I like you the best.
谢谢你 菲比 你嘴真甜
Thank you,Pheebs. That's very sweet.
有听到吗?
You hear that?
她最喜欢我 而且很显然 你阅人无数
She likes me best.And apparently,there have been a lot.
没有很多啦
Not a lot.
菲比只是开玩笑 她疯了
Phoebe's kidding. Phoebe's crazy.
菲比完蛋了
Phoebe's dead.
我来找艾迪曼诺维克
I'm looking for Eddie Manoick.
他人现在不在 我是钱德
He's not here right now.I'm Chandler.
你要留个言还是… 留下鱼缸?
Can I take a message or... Or a fish tank?
谢了
Thanks.
进来吧
Come on in.
我是堤莉
I'm Tilly.
听得出来 他聊过我的事了
I gather by that"Oh," he told you about me.
没错 是有提过你的名字...
Yeah,your name came up...
在一个令我惊心动魄的谈话中
in a conversation that terrified me to my very soul.
他很激烈 对吧?
He's kind of intense,huh?
没错!问你个问题 艾迪是不是有点…?
Yes!Can I ask you,is Eddie a little..
一点怎样?      有点乡村?
A little what?        bit country?
进来吧 室友
Come on in,you roomie!
你好 堤莉
Hello,Tilly.
艾迪 我只是把鱼缸 拿过来给你
Eddie,I just came by to drop off your tank.
你真的很周到
That was very thoughtful of you.
真的很周到
It's very thoughtful.
那好吧
Well,okay then.
我要走了 再见
I'm gonna go.Bye.
所以我们要养鱼吗?
So we getting a fish?
你和她上过床了 对不对?
You had sex with her,didn't you?
菲比 快来看!
Pheebs!Check it out,check it out!
是《肥皂剧文摘》 我的最爱之一
Soap Opera Digest! That's one of my favorite digests!
快看第四十二页
Page 42! Page 42!
"《我们的日子》医界新秀 乔伊崔比亚尼"
"NewDoc on the Block, Days of our Lives Joey Tribbiani.
好耶      好棒的照片
Yeah.Yeah.         Oh,cool picture!
我看起来真棒
Oh,I look good.
这是真的吗? 你很多台词都是自己写的?
Is this true? That you write a lot of your own lines?
算是啦
Well,kind of, yeah.
记得上星期亚莉发生意外吗?
Remember last week when Alex was in the accident?
原本的台词是...
The line in the script was...
"如果不把她送到医院 她就会死掉"
"If we don'tget this woman to a hospital,she's going to die."
但是我把它改成 "如果不把她送到医院...
But I made it,"If this woman doesn't get to a hospital...
她就活不成了"
she's not gonna live."
噢 我懂你做了什么了
Oh, okay.I see what you did there.
你不怕编剧读到这个时会生气吗?
Aren't you afraid the writers will be kind of mad when they read this?
我真的从没想过编剧 剧本总是送到我家
I never thought about the writers.The scripts just come to my house.
但是你知道吗?
But you know what?
这让我有面子 也让节目有面子...
This makes me look good,which makes the show look good...
编剧也有面子 他们怎么可能会生气 对吧?
which makes the writers look good.So how could they be mad?
很多台词都是自己写的
Makes up most of his lines.
这个臭…
Son of a...
好 我就写给你看
Yeah.Write this,jerkweed.
我从电梯井跌下去?
I fall down an elevator shaft?
这什么意思? 我从电梯井跌下去?
What does this mean? I fall down an elevator shaft?
我不知道 我只是送剧本的
Uh,I don't know.I just bring the scripts.
他们不能杀掉我 我可是弗朗西斯卡失散的儿子
They can't kill me!I'm Francesca's long-lost son!
是啊
Right.
你可以签收吗?
Could you sign?
不要!我才不签
No!No way!I'm not signing that!
我不认为这会影响剧情
I dont think that's gonna affect the plot of the show.
他们怎么可以这样对我?
How can they do this to me
好 我要走了
All right,I'm just gonna go.
很遗憾
Sorry.
也没有那么多啦
Well,it wasn't that many guys.
如果你想想 这世上有多少男人的话...
If you consider how many guys there actually are...
比例其实很小
it's a very small percentage.
没什么大不了的 我只是好奇而已
It's not that big a deal. I was just curious.
晚安      晚安 理查
Good night.        Good night, Richard.
祝你好运 摩妮卡
Good luck,Mon.
好吧 在我说之前 先说你和几位女性交往过
All right,before I tell you,you tell me how many women you've been with.
两个      两个?两个?
Two.         Two? Two?
怎么可能?我的意思是...
How is that possible? I mean...
你知道自己有多帅吗?
have you seen you?
我能说什么呢?
Well I mean,what can I say
我和芭芭拉做了三十年的夫妻 我们高中就认识了
I was married to Barbara for 30 years,my high-school sweetheart.
再加上你 就是两个人
Now you. That's two.
那就两个吧
Two it is.
好 该睡觉了 我先去刷牙
Okay,time for bed.I'm gonna brush my teeth.
不行 等等!
No,wait a minute now!
别这样 轮到你了
Come on.It's your turn.
快说呀
Oh,come on!
我不需要确切的数字 差不多就行了
You know,I don't need the actual number.Just a ballpark.
好 绝对没有棒球场的人多
Okay,it is definitely less than a ballpark.
哇 真庆幸我不是摩妮卡
Wow, I am so glad I'm not Monica right now.
那还用说
Tell me about it.
那你的神奇数字是多少?
So,what's your magic number?
别这样 我交往过的你都认识 两个都知道
Come on,you know everyone Ive been with. All both of them.
嗯 有你
Well,there's you.
最好不要说我是第一个
Better not be doing these in order
好 比利 彼特
Okay,Billy Dreskin,Pete Carny.
巴瑞
Barry.
还有 巴洛
And,Paolo.
是啊 那个托里尼来的蠢蛋
Oh, yes,the weenie from Turinie.
噢 亲爱的 你嫉妒保罗吗?
Oh, honey,are you jealous of Paolo?
我跟你在一起 比跟他快乐多了
I'mso much happier with you than I ever was with him.
真的吗?      拜托
Really?        Oh, please.
跟保罗那段根本就不能算
That Paolo thing was barely a relationship.
充其量只是无意义的 野兽的性关系
All it really was was just meaningless,animal sex.
嗯 那句话在我脑海里 听起来好很多
Okay,you know,that sounded so much better in my head.
艾迪 我没有和你的前女友上床
Eddie!I didn't sleep with your ex-girlfriend.
真有趣 跟她睡过的人 就会这么说
That's exactly what someone who slept with her would say.
太疯狂了! 她只待了两分钟...
This is nuts! Crazy! She came over for two minutes...
留下鱼缸就走了 就这样
dropped off a fish tank and left! End of story.
巴迪在哪里?      巴迪?
Where's Buddy?         Buddy?
我的鱼 巴迪
My fish,Buddy.
她来的时候没有鱼啊
There was no fish when she dropped it off
噢 真是无法置信!
Oh.this is unbelievable!
你先是跟我的前女友上床 再说谎侮辱我的智商...
You sleep with my exgirifriend,insult my intelligence by lying..
然后杀掉我的鱼? 我的巴迪?
then you kill my fish? My Buddy?
我没有杀掉你的鱼
I didn't kill your fish!
听着 艾迪...
Look, Eddie..
看看我在做什么
Would you look at what I'm doing?
绝对不是明智之举
Now that cant be smart.
所以我们把这个家伙从你身上拿开...
So we're just gonna take this guy right off you...
把他放到口袋先生里
and put him here in Mr. Pocket.
来颗橘子吗?
Tangelo?
就这样?你就这么害怕告诉我那庞大的数目?
Thats it? That's the giant number you were afraid to tell me?
是的
oh yeah
那不会太糟啊
Well,that's not bad at all.
我还以为有一整个舰队呢
You had me thinking it was,like,a fleet.
你真的不介意?
You're okay with it?
亲爱的 我没问题
Oh, honey,Im fine.
好 关于你那两个人
Okay,about that two.
什么?
What?
好
All right.
我那两个人怎么了?
What about my two?
只是真的好少喔
It just seems like a really small number
对啊
Right.
你难道没有欲望到处去采花吗?
Don't you have a lot of wild oats to sow?
你现在就是那样对我吗? 天啊 我是花吗?
Or is that what you're doing with me? Oh, my God! Am I an oat?
亲爱的 你不是被采的花
Honey, you are not an oat.
我也不知道 我不是那种采花大盗
I don't know,I guess I'm just not an oat guy.
我只和我爱的人上床
I've only slept with women I love.
但你只跟两个人上过床
You've only slept with two people.
对
Right.
你知道我也爱你吧?
You know I love you too, right?
我现在知道了
Now I do.
罗斯!
Ross!
罗斯 请你听我说
Ross, please listen to me.
罗斯 你比巴洛好太多了
Ross, you are so much better for me than Paolo ever was.
你关心我 你爱我 你逗我笑
You care about me,you're loving,you make me laugh.
那样的话 我有个主意
If I make you laugh,here's an idea.
你就邀请巴洛过来野性一下 我就站在角落...
Invite Paolo to have a romp in the sack,and I'll stand in the corner...
讲些笑话给你听      罗斯!
and tell knockknock jokes.         Ross!
天啊 罗斯!
God, Ross!
你和我的关系很特别 巴洛和我只是…
What you and I have is special! All Paolo and I ever had was
野兽的性关系?
Animal sex animal sex?
你是什么意思?
So,what are you saying?
我们之间完全没有野性吗?
There's nothing between us "animal" at all?
连一点兽性都没有吗?
There's not even like,a little animal?
连...
Not even like...
花粟鼠性关系都没有?
chipmunk sex?
好 罗斯…
Okay, Ross...
试着听进我说的话
Try to hear me, okay?
嘿 我不会对你说谎
I Hey.Im not gonna lie to you.
跟巴洛很棒      笑话来了
It was good with Paolo.         Knock-knock.
但你和我的关系比那好太多了
But what you and I have is so much better.
我们之间有温柔 有亲密 灵犀相通
We have tenderness,we have intimacy,we connect.
是真的 我发誓
You know? I swear
到目前为止...
This is the best...
这是我有过最棒的
I have ever had.
直到这一刻
Until now.
理查刚刚告诉我他爱我
Richard told me he loved me.
天啊!      是啊!
Oh, my God!         l know!
实在太棒了
Honey,that's great!
对啊
I know!
我只是找不到...      最上面的抽屉
I just cant find...        Top drawer.
快点      为什么?你也要吗?
Hurry.         Why? You need one too?
没错
Oh, yeah.
找到了
Found them!
只有一个
There's only one.
摩妮卡!
Monica!
很快就好 我们要决定一点事情
Uh,we'll be right there.We're just trying to decide something.
瑞秋?
Rachel?
她们只是要决定一点事情
They're trying to decide something.
哦 好的 好 好
oh Good good good
那么你的胡子 以前是不是不一样?
So was your mustache Did it used to be different?
没有
No
你是怎么保持得这么整齐?
How do you,you know,keep it so neat?
我有把小梳子
I have a little comb.
什么样的梳子?      胡子梳
What do you call that?        A mustache comb.
谢谢
Thank you.
好 我会洗你一个月的衣服
Okay,I will do your laundry for one month.
不要!
No!
我会 我会…
I will I will...
我会打扫两个月的公寓
I will clean the apartment for two months.
我可以马上给你 只要你告诉我畚箕放在哪里
I'll give this to you now,if you tell me where we keep the dustpan.
你有没有打过越战?
So were you in Nam?
剪刀 石头 布?      没问题
Rock,paper,scissors?         Gotcha.
一 二 三
One,two,three.
太好了
Yes!
好吧 去上床吧
Fine. Go have sex.
不对!你完全搞错了!
No!You have got it completely wrong!
约翰萨维奇演出 《越战猎鹿人》 他没有腿
John Savage was Deer Hunter, no legs.
强沃特演出《归返家园》 腿瘫痪了
Jon Voight was Coming Home, couldn't feel his legs.
不对 你完全搞错了 强沃特...
No,you've got it totally the other way around,my friend.Jon Voight
亲爱的?      干嘛?
Honey?          What?
进去吧      今晚不可能了
Shall we?         It's not gonna happen.
今晚他们做 我们可以明天再做
They're doing it tonight. We can do it tomorrow.
下一次的时间表 可不可以先让我看看?
In the future,if I could see the schedule beforehand...
我今天早上起来时...
So when I woke up this morning...
他偷走我所有鞋子的鞋垫!
he'd stolen all the insoles out of my shoes!
为什么?
Why?
因为他认为我和他的前女友上床 而且杀掉他的鱼
He thinks I slept with his ex-girlfriend and killed his fish.
你为什么要杀掉他的鱼?
Why would you kill his fish?
因为有时候你和某人睡过以后...
Because sometimes after you sleep with someone...
就得杀掉一条鱼
you have to kill a fish.
钱德 宝贝...
Chandler,honey...
真的很遗憾
I'm sorry.
现在可以看乔伊的节目了吗?
Can we watch Joey's show now,please?
是啊!      等等 他还没到
Yeah!         Wait.He's not here yet.
他有演出 他知道情节
He's on the show,he knows what happens.
对了 我不在乎我的问题了
I'm fine about my problem now,by the way.
安珀...
Amber...
你需要的时候 永远有我在身边...
I want you to know I'll always be there for you...
我是你一辈子的朋友跟兄弟
as a friend and as your brother
噢 德瑞克
Oh,Drake.
辛苦的一天吧?
Hard day,huh?
先是医学大奖 然后是这个?
First the medical award, now this?
是呀 我猜有人天生好运
Some guys are just lucky, I guess. Ha, ha.
雷莫瑞医生 请到一楼急诊室报到
Dr.Ramoray,report to first floor Emergency stat.
那么...
Well then...
我想我得走了
I guess that's me.
还有人要进电梯吗? 何医生?王医生?
Anyone else need to go on the elevator? Dr. Horton? Dr. Wong?
不 他们只有说你
No, no.They only said you.
噢 好吧
Oh, okay. All right.
我爱你 德瑞克      随便啦
I love you, Drake.         Yeah whatever.
不!      德瑞克 小心啊!
Oh no!        Drake. look out!
他们让乔伊死掉?      不会吧
Did they just kill off Joey?         No!
或许吧
Now maybe.
快点开门 我们要跟你说话
Come on! Open up! We want to talk to you!
我不想说话
I don't feel like talking!
别这样 我们很关心你
Come on! We care about you.
我们很担心你      有些人得尿尿!
We're worried about you.        And some of us have to pee!
对不起 乔伊
I'm sorry, Joey.
很遗憾你死了 真的烂透了
Listen, sorry about your death. That really sucks.
我们一看到就赶过来了      你怎么没跟我们说?
We came over as soon as we saw.         How could you not tell us?
我不知道 我希望 没有人会知道
I don't know.I was kind of hoping no one would ever find out.
或许他们有办法让你起死回生
Well,maybe they could find a way to bring you back.
不会的 他们说尸体的大脑 已经摔得稀巴烂了...
No,they said that when they found my body,my brain was so smashed in...
唯一能救我的人是我
that the only doctor who could've saved me was me.
还说这是某种讽刺之类的
Its supposed to be some kind of irony.
但是乔伊 你不会有事的
But Joey,you're gonna be fine.
你不需要那个节目 那只是个蠢肥皂剧
You don'tneed that show. It was just a dumb soap opera.
这是我这辈子 最棒的事
This was the greatest thing that ever happened to me.
对 我正要说到那一点
Yes!I was going to incorporate that.
太好了 摩妮卡来了 她会说句好听的
Oh, good,here's Monica. She'll have something nice to say.
我把你的浴帘拉直了免得发霉
I straightened out your shower curtain so you won't get mildew.
干嘛?那是好事啊
What? To me,that's nice.
不会有事的 你知道的
It's gonna be okay.You know that.
我不知道
No.I don't.
这好像你奋斗了一辈子 追求某样东西...
It's like you work your whole life for something...
当你以为你办到的时候...
and you think that when you get it...
永远不会像你想得那么好
it'll never be as good as you thought would be.
不过这个是啊
But this so was.
它改变了一切
It changed everything.
前几天 我去申请信用卡...
Like,the other day,I got this credit card application...
我竟然被预先核准!
and I was preapproved!
我这辈子从没被预先核准过!
I've never been preapproved for anything in my life!
真的很遗憾
I'm sorry, man.
我不知道这样 对你有没有意义…
I don't know if this'll mean anything to you...
但你在我们之中 永远都是预先核准
but you'll always be preapproved with us.
没有 一点意义都没有
No,that means nothing to me.
要吃大胡桃饼吗? 刚出炉的
Pecan sandy? Just made them.
好啊
Yeah, all right.
这是葡萄干吗?
Are these raisins?
有何不可?
sure,why not?
听着 艾迪
Listen,Eddie.
我想过我们目前 住在一起的情况了
I've been thinking about our living situation.
你在笑什么?
Why are you smiling?
我有个小惊喜 有条新鱼
I got a little surprise. Look.There's a new fishy.
我把它命名为
I named him,
钱德 以你为名
Chandler,you know,after you.
那根本不是条真鱼
Well,that's not even a real fish.
那只是金鱼饼干
No,that's a Goldfish cracker.
什么意思?
So.what's your point,man?
好 晚安了
Okay,good night.
你这个大怪胎
You big freak of nature.
今晚好冷      是啊
Brisk tonight.         Oh. man.
这件事永远都不要提      没问题
Let's never speak of this.         You got it.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧